http://www.education.act.gov.au/functions/privacy

Public Health Emergency in the ACTA Public Health Emergency has been declared in the ACT for the response to the COVID-19 pandemic. Read more
Early Childhood
Information about Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) for Education and Care Services
Positive Behaviour for Learning
Positive Behaviour, Mental Health and Wellbeing Approaches in our Schools
Reportable Conduct Scheme
Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Employment Action Plan
Work In Canberra
Who are we?
Pay and Conditions
New Educator Support Professional Learning
Why Canberra?
Early Childhood
Information about Novel Coronavirus (COVID-19) for Education and Care Services
Positive Behaviour for Learning
Positive Behaviour, Mental Health and Wellbeing Approaches in our Schools
Reportable Conduct Scheme
Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Employment Action Plan
Work In Canberra
Who are we?
Pay and Conditions
New Educator Support Professional Learning
Why Canberra?
Privacy
The Australian Capital Territory Government has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting personal privacy. This statement addresses collection, use, security of and access to information that may be obtained through the use of the ACT Education Directorate web sites. This notice covers the following topics:Privacy ActInformation collectedPurpose for collecting this information and use of informationOther privacy issues:CookiesGoogle AnalyticsSecurityDisclaimer for external linksContact detailsThe ACT Education Directorate website complies with the requirements for Commonwealth and ACT Government websites namely the Privacy Act 1988 and the Privacy Commissioner's Guidelines for Federal and ACT Government World Wide Web portals.Privacy ActWith respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information, ACT Education Directorate is bound by the Information Privacy Act 2014Information collectedWhen you visit the ACT Education Directorate website to browse or download information, we automatically collect and store the following information about your visit:The Internet Protocol address and a component of the domain name used (eg: .com, .net, .gov, .au, etc.). The Internet Protocol address is a numerical identifier assigned either by your Internet service provider or directly to your computer. We use the Internet Protocol address to direct Internet traffic to you where this is required;The type of browser and operating system you used;The date and time you visited this website;The web pages or services you accessed at this website;The time spent on individual pages and the website overall; andWhich files are downloadedThe website also collects contact information (eg. email address). However, we do not use these details unless you choose to provide this information. The reason for collecting this information will be displayed on the appropriate page. In that event your details will only be used for the purpose for which you provided them and will not be added to any mailing list unless you ask for this to be done.We collect no personal information about you unless you voluntarily participate in an activity that asks for information (i.e. sending an e-mail, participating in a survey or completing a form). If you choose not to participate in these activities, your choice will in no way affect your ability to use any other feature of the ACT Education Directorate's websites.Purpose for collecting this information and use of informationThe information we automatically collect or store is used to improve the content of our web services and to help us to understand how people are using our services. Information you provide in relation to surveys, forms or feedback is strictly used for the purpose you provided it.The ACT Education Directorate analyses the website logs to continually improve the value of the services available on our site. Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that browse the ACT Education Directorate websites.Other information you provide voluntarily is used for delivering the documents or services you requested and in case we need extra information for clarification. We use your e-mail or other details to contact you: this may be to advise receipt, to address issues you identify, to further improve our web site, or to forward the details to another agency for appropriate action. Survey information is used for the purpose designated. Where information is provided to another agency, a statement in accordance with the Information Privacy Principles 1 to 3 in the Privacy Act 1988 as to whom the information is supplied and for what purpose will be clearly identified on the appropriate page of the form.Other privacy issuesFollowing are some other privacy issues that we consider relevant:CookiesCookies are simple text files stored on your computer by your web browser. They provide a method of distinguishing among visitors to the ACT Education Directorate websites.Cookies created on your computer by using this website do not contain personally identifying information and do not compromise your privacy or security. We use the cookie feature only to store a randomly generated identifying tag on your computer. You can refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer by using any of the widely available methods.Cookies can be removed at any time from your hard drive.Google AnalyticsThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (Google). Google Analytics uses cookies and JavaScript code to enable analysis on usage of this website. The data collected about your use of this website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored on Google's servers. Google will use this data for the purpose of compiling reports on website activity for the ACT Education Directorate and provide other services relating to website activity and Internet usage.Google will not collect personal information about you. The reports provided by Google to us will only contain aggregate non-personal data about your use of this website, (these reports may contain data relating to pages viewed, files downloaded or the completion of online subscriptions). The ACT Education Directorate will use the data collected by Google Analytics to improve the functionality of this website.Google may transfer this data to third parties where required to do so by law, or where third parties process this data on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any personal information you may have previously provided to Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. Please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out aboveSecurityThis site does not provide facilities for the secure transmission of information across the internet. Users should be aware that there are inherent risks in transmitting information across the internet.Disclaimer for External LinksThe ACT Education Directorate websites have links to other websites. These include links to websites operated by other government agencies, organisations, private individuals and businesses. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our websites and this Privacy Statement will not apply. When you link to another website, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site.Neither the ACT Government, nor any agency, officer, or employee of the ACT Government warrants the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published by this system, nor endorses any content, viewpoints, products, or services linked from this system, and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information. Portions of such information may be incorrect or not current. Any person or entity that relies on any information obtained from this system does so at his or her own risk.To offer comments about ACT Education Directorate websites, or about the information presented in this Privacy Statement, you can use the feedback form or the ACT Education Directorate contact details below.Contact DetailsTo offer comments about the ACT Education Directorate websites, or about the information presented in this Privacy Statement, you can use the feedback form on this website or the ACT Education Directorate contact details.
Top
